- [Man] What's wrong?
- What's wrong?
Who is this girl at the store
that you keep looking at?
What is this interaction
going on between you and her?
- I don't know what
you're talking about.
- You don't know what
I'm talking about.
- I was in the store with you.
Why would I be looking
at somebody else?
- You were looking
at somebody else.
You going to continue
to deny this?
Let me out of the car.
- Why'd we have to keep
going through this?
- Yeah, why do we have to
keep going through this?
Let me out of the car.
- Babe.
(slow music with vocalization)
♪ Darlin' I, I can't explain ♪
♪ Where did we lose our way ♪
♪ Girl it's drivin' me insane ♪
♪ And I know I just
need one more chance ♪
♪ To prove my love to you ♪
♪ And if you come back to me ♪
♪ I'll guarantee ♪
♪ That I'll never let you go ♪
♪ Can we go back to the
days our love was strong ♪
♪ Can you tell me how a
perfect love goes wrong ♪
♪ Can somebody tell me
how to get things back ♪
♪ The way they used to be ♪
♪ Oh God, give me a reason ♪
♪ I'm down on bended knee ♪
♪ I'll never walk again
until you come back to me ♪
♪ I'm down on bended knee ♪
♪ So many nights
I dream of you ♪
♪ Holding my pillow tight ♪
♪ And I know that I don't
need to be alone, yeah ♪
♪ When I open up my eyes ♪
♪ To face reality ♪
♪ Every moment without you ♪
♪ It seems like eternity ♪
♪ I'm begging you, begging
you come back to me ♪
♪ Can we go back to the
days our love was strong ♪
♪ Can you tell me how a
perfect love goes wrong ♪
♪ Can somebody tell me
how to get things back ♪
♪ The way they used to be ♪
♪ Oh God, give me a reason ♪
♪ I'm down on bended knee ♪
♪ I'll never walk again
until you come back to me ♪
♪ I'm down on bended knee ♪
- Baby, I'm sorry.
Please forgive me for
all the wrong I've done.
Please come back home, girl.
I know you put all
your trust in me.
I'm sorry I let you down.
Please forgive me.
♪ I'm gonna swallow my pride ♪
♪ Say I'm sorry ♪
♪ Stop pointing fingers,
the blame is on me ♪
♪ I want a new life ♪
♪ And I want it with you ♪
♪ If you feel the same ♪
♪ Don't ever let it go ♪
♪ You gotta believe in
the spirit of love ♪
♪ It'll heal all things ♪
♪ It won't hurt anymore ♪
♪ No, I don't believe
our love's terminal ♪
♪ I'm down on my knees
begging you please come home ♪
♪ Can we go back to the
days our love was strong ♪
♪ Can we come back, baby,
I just want to come back ♪
♪ Can you tell me how a
perfect love goes wrong ♪
♪ Can somebody tell me
how to get things back ♪
♪ The way they used to be ♪
♪ Oh God, give me a reason ♪
♪ I'm down on bended ♪
♪ Down on bended knee ♪
♪ Can we go back to the
days our love was strong ♪
♪ Can you tell me how a
perfect love goes wrong ♪
♪ Want to make you my
wife, raise a family ♪
♪ Can somebody tell me
how to get things back ♪
♪ The way they used to be ♪
♪ Oh God, give me a reason ♪
♪ Give me a reason ♪
♪ I'm down on bended knee ♪
♪ I'll never walk again ♪
♪ 'Til you come back to me ♪
♪ I'm down on bended knees ♪